https://www.unicarrierseurope.com/en/privacy-policy

OLP / OEP | Low-level order pickers | OLP / OEP
OLH / OEH | Low level order pickers with driver lift | OLH / OEH
TERGO® ULS
| Narrow-chassis reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® ULS
TERGO® UND | Narrow-chassis reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® UND
TERGO® UMS | Universal reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® UMS
TERGO® UMS-TF/UHD-TF/UHX-TF | Reach trucks with telescopic forks | TERGO® UMS-TF/UHD-TF/UHX-TF
COVID-19
Contact usI want to buy a truckFor purchases of new and used forklifts
I want to hire a truckFor short or long-term forklift hire
I need service on my forkliftFor service or spare parts enquiries
Remember my choice next time
MarketBelgique / België | Français / NederlandsDanmark | DanskDeutschland | DeutschEspaña | EspañolFrance | FrançaisItalia | ItalianoNederland | NederlandsNorge | NorskPolska | PolskiSverige | SvenskaTürkiye | TürkçeUnited Kingdom | EnglishUnicarrierseurope.com English
You are hereHome/Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy was first published on 25/05/2018, and last updated on 01/04/2020
At Mitsubishi Logisnext Europe we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, website visitors and other contacts in compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). On this page you can find information about what personal information we may collect from you, why we collect it, and how we use it and keep it secure.
Who are we?
MLE Group Office Filial is a part of Mitsubishi Logisnext Europe (MLE), a manufacturer and supplier of material handling equipment and solutions.
The address of our office is:
MLE Group Office FilialMetallvägen 9435 33 MölnlyckeSweden
The company’s organisation number is 516412-2276.
When do we collect personal data about you?
Website VisitorsWhen you fill in one of the forms on our website – for example, to make a business enquiry, or to subscribe to a blog. If you do not provide us your personal data via one of our forms, we cannot collect personal identifying data about you via the website, however your anonymised IP address may be recorded.
Job applicants & studentsWhen applying for an open job position, internship or master thesis at MLE.
CustomersWhen you become a customer of MLE (whether you are purchasing products or solutions, or training and education services), we collect personal information in order to be able to get in contact with you and maintain our business relationship.
SuppliersWhen you establish contact or sign contracts with MLE as a supplier or potential supplier.
Why do we collect and use this personal data?
Website Visitors & CustomersWe use your personal data for the purposes of marketing or for customer service.
We may use your information for these purposes:
o   Sending you marketing communications which you have requested – for example, information about our products and services, blog posts or other content which may be interesting to you, or events and campaigns that we are involved with.
o   Sending you blog alerts when a new post is published, on any blogs that you have subscribed to.
o   Replying to or following up on a business request you have made via one of our forms (for example, giving an answer to a question you have asked about a product or service).
o   Maintaining a business relationship with you by storing contact information and information about past contact in a CRM system.
o   Booking training courses you have applied for and issuing training certificates.
Job applicants & studentsFor job applications or student placements we use personal data in order to establish contact and to determine suitability for the job.
SuppliersWe use personal data in order to be able to sign contracts and maintain the correct contact information for our suppliers.
What legal basis do we have for collecting personal data?
Website VisitorsConsent  – We only collect your personal data when you consent to us collecting it at the point it is collected. For example, when you submit one of our contact forms, you will have to consent for us to collect your data via the form.
Job applicants & studentsFor job applications we rely on legitimate interest and legal obligations.
SuppliersFor current and potential suppliers we base our processing of personal data on an established contract or on a legitimate interest in order to pursue a business relation.
CustomersFor current and potential customers we base our processing of personal data on an established contract or on a legitimate interest in order to pursue a business relation.
What type of personal data do we collect?
Website VisitorsWhen you fill out a contact form, we may collect your name, your company, the address and city/town of your company, your email address and your telephone number. However, we may not necessarily ask for all of these types of personal data. On the website we may also collect your IP address and record activities made on the website – for example, viewing a certain page, or clicking a particular button.
We do not collect or store any ‘special categories of personal data’ as described in the GDPR.
Job applicants & studentsFor job applications we collect basic contact information, application letter, Curriculum Vitae, and Behavioural Profile, reference contacts and their evaluation.
CustomersFor customers and potential customers, we may collect basic contact information such as name, business email address, phone number, as well as the business address. In the case of customers who have received training at the Competence and Training Centre, we will also collect the social security number. Information relating to previous deals and meetings may also be stored.
SuppliersFor current and potential suppliers we collect name, contact information for the following roles: Sales, Quality, and Logistics.
How long do we keep your personal data?
Website VisitorsWhen you give us your personal data via a contact form on the website, we store it for as long as we think it is needed for us to carry out whatever task you originally gave it to us for, or to make it possible for us to properly help you in the future. For example, if you have chosen to subscribe to a blog, your personal data will be stored as long as you remain subscribed, so that you can be sent update emails when new posts are published. If you request it, your personal information will promptly be securely deleted.
Job applicants & studentsFor Job applications we save your data during ongoing recruitment and two years after.
CustomersWhen we store your information in our CRM system, we store it for as long as we think it is needed for us to carry out whatever task you originally gave it to us for, or to make it possible for us to properly help you in the future – for example, to see what equipment you may have purchased in the past.
SuppliersWe keep your data during the contract period and for as long there is an ongoing business interest between the companies.
What rights do you have relating to your personal data?
You have the right to request all of the following:
·        A copy of all your personal data that we have. This is to be delivered in a machine-readable format.
·        That we update or change your personal data.
·        That we delete all or some of your personal data.
·        That we stop processing or partly stop processing your personal data, whether we currently hold your personal data or not.
If you want to make one of these requests, you can email privacy [at] unicarrierseurope.com
How do we use cookies?
The cookies we use collect certain pieces of information as you browse the website, such as your browser, your IP address, and what actions you take on the website. We use cookies to give you a better experience when you use the website – for example, by sending you to the correct local website for your country. You can find out more detailed information about cookies on our cookie policy page.
Do we share your data with anyone else?
We don’t share with or sell your data to anyone else outside of the MLE group, unless we need to involve a third party (distributors, dealers and other partners) to fulfill your request.
Does anyone else have access to your personal data? (Processors and sub-processors)
Some third parties that we work with may have access to the personal data that you have given to us via the website – for example, external agencies and suppliers that have access to the software we use to store personal data. We make sure that these third parties comply with our privacy policies.
Do we change our privacy policy?
This policy may change or be updated from time to time. If there are any major changes to our privacy policy or how we use your data, we will notify you.
How can I make a privacy complaint?
If you want to complain to use about how we collect or use your data, you can email privacy [at] unicarrierseurope.com.
However, you can also complain directly to your country’s authority for data protection, such as Information Commissioner’s Office in the United Kingdom, or Datainspektionen in Sweden.
VISIT:
My UniCarriers
VISIT US ON:
About us
Why UniCarriers?
Products
Pallet trucks
MDW / MDE | Compact pedestrian pallet truck | MDW / MDE
ALL/XLL | Stand-in and sit-on low lifters | ALL/XLL
PLF | Pallet truck with folding platform | PLF
PLR | Rear-entry pallet truck with fixed platform | PLR
PLS | Side-entry pallet truck with fixed platform | PLS
Stackers
OLP / OEP | Low-level order pickers | OLP / OEP
OLH / OEH | Low level order pickers with driver lift | OLH / OEH
EPL | Medium-level order picker | EPL
EPM / EPH | Medium and high-level order pickers | EPM / EPH
OTP | Tow tractor and logistic train | OTP
View all
Reach trucks
TERGO® ULS
| Narrow-chassis reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® ULS
TERGO® UND | Narrow-chassis reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® UND
TERGO® UMS | Universal reach truck for medium lift heights | TERGO® UMS
TERGO® UMS-TF/UHD-TF/UHX-TF | Reach trucks with telescopic forks | TERGO® UMS-TF/UHD-TF/UHX-TF
TERGO® UFW | Multi-directional reach truck | TERGO® UFW
View all
Very Narrow Aisle Trucks
TERGO® URS | Man-down VNA truck | TERGO® URS
EK | Man-up VNA truck | EK
Electric counterbalance forklift trucks
TX3 | 48V three-wheel counterbalance truck | TX3
TX4 | 48V Four-wheel counterbalance truck | TX4
Contact us
How can we help you?
I want to buy a truckFor purchases of new and used forklifts
I want to hire a truckFor short or long-term forklift hire
I need service on my forkliftFor service or spare parts enquiries
Questions?For questions about our trucks and solutions
CREATING DIFFERENCE
UniCarriers
Cookies
Privacy Policy
Choose language
Remember my choice next time
MarketBelgique / België | Français / NederlandsDanmark | DanskDeutschland | DeutschEspaña | EspañolFrance | FrançaisItalia | ItalianoNederland | NederlandsNorge | NorskPolska | PolskiSverige | SvenskaTürkiye | TürkçeUnited Kingdom | EnglishUnicarrierseurope.com English
